survivorsrest.com 2018-04-12

# Privacy Policy - Survivors Rest

This privacy policy sets out how Survivors Rest uses and protects any information that you give Survivors Rest when you use this website.

Survivors Rest is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

Survivors Rest may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from January 23rd, 2015.

#### What we collect

We may collect the following information:  

  * If you create an account, we will collect your Steam Name, your Steam ID and your Steam Profile Image and optionally your Email address.
  * If you interact with us by sending comments or suggestions or by posting or sharing content on social media platforms such as Facebook, Twitter and Reddit, we may collect personal information such as your opinion, interests, preferences and degree of satisfaction with our products and services.

#### What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:  

  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * If you have opted in we may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * To answer your questions and follow-up with your support queries;
  * To prevent, deter and investigate violation of this Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions, or any fraud and other illegal activities;
  * To send information on our products and services, to the extent permitted by law;
  * For any other purpose authorized or required by law.

#### Disclosure of personal information to Third Parties

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

#### What non-personal information we collect from you

  * Log Information: We automatically collect and store standard internet log information when you visit the Website. This information may include, but is not limited to, your Uniform Resource Locator ("URL"), your Internet Protocol ("IP") address and domain name used, your type of browser, the date, time and length of your visits as well as the searches conducted and the web pages consulted.
  * Cookies: Cookies are small data files that store information on your computer’s hard drive or web browser. They enable the Website to identify your computer and recognize that you have accessed the Website before.

#### Age

We do not intend to collect, use or disclose personal information from anyone under the age of 18 without verifiable parental consent. If you are under 13 years old, you are not allowed to use our Website. If we learn that we have collected personal information from anyone under the age of 18, we will take steps to delete the information as soon as possible.

#### Right to Access and Correct

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please use our Contact form.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete you can correct most of the information youself, in you are aunable to please contact us via our Contact form as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

#### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

#### Servers

Our servers are located in the United Kingdom. If you are accessing the Website from outside the United Kingdom, please be advised that by your continued use of this Website, you consent to the transfer, processing and storage of your personal information in the United Kingdom and to make use of services whose use are governed by the laws and jurisdiction of the United Kingdom.

#### How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

#### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

#### Google Analytics

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses "cookies", which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. In case IP-anonymisation is activated on this website, your IP address will be truncated within the area of Member States of the European Union or other parties to the Agreement on the European Economic Area. Only in exceptional cases the whole IP address will be first transfered to a Google server in the USA and truncated there. The IP-anonymisation is active on this website. Google will use this information on behalf of the operator of this website for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing them other services relating to website activity and internet usage. The IP-address, that your Browser conveys within the scope of Google Analytics, will not be associated with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. You can also opt-out from being tracked by Google Analytics with effect for the future by downloading and installing Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Addon for your current web browser: [http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en).
